phonepower.com 2017-10-21

# Phone Power - Privacy Policy | VoIP Service & FREE VoIP Phone Calls

Phone Power is committed to protecting the privacy and security of the information provided by customers visiting our Web site or using our services. Phone Power may request information from people visiting our Web sites or using our services. Phone Power is the sole owner of the information collected. Phone Power respects your privacy and will not knowingly distribute or cause to be distributed your personal information to any entity for any reason. We will not collect any personally identifiable information unless the visitor/customer provides it to us voluntarily. Personally identifiable information includes a visitors/customer’s name, address, telephone number and e-mail address. Phone Power is dedicated to building a long-term relationship with all of our customers and visitors. We will not sell, share or rent this information to others in ways other than as disclosed in this Privacy Policy. 

**Prequalification and Service Quotes:** In some cases, a visitor may be required to complete a prequalification or inquiry form to order a product or to receive certain information. During the registration process, the visitor is required to give specific information such as name and e-mail address, mailing address, location and phone number. This information is used to pre-qualify and contact the visitor regarding services offered by Phone Power for which the visitor has expressed interest. 

**Ordering:** When taking orders online, Phone Power will request certain information from a customer to complete an order. The customer's information will include name, address, telephone number, e-mail address, payment information and other information as may be requested by Phone Power in the order form. This information is used for billing purposes, fulfillment of orders, ongoing account maintenance and upgrades. 

**Security:** When customers are asked to enter certain sensitive information (such as credit card number and/or social security number), that information is encrypted and is protected through a Secure Socket Layer (SSL). SSL negotiates and employs the essential functions of mutual authentication, data encryption and data integrity for secure transactions. While on a secure page, such as an order form, the lock icon on the bottom of Web browsers such as Microsoft Internet Explorer® and Netscape Navigator® becomes locked, as opposed to unlocked, or open, when you are viewing other Web sites. 

All customer/visitor information, not just the sensitive information mentioned above, is restricted to Phone Power developers, network operations personnel and other qualified employees (such as billing clerks or customer care representatives). Finally, the servers on which Phone Power stores personally identifiable information are kept in a secure location. 

**Cookies:** A "Cookie" is a piece of information that is sent from a Phone Power Web server to a visitor's browser and stored on the visitor's hard drive. Phone Power uses Cookies when a visitor orders a product or registers for a specific program. The Cookie stores information that allows Phone Power Web sites to remember a visitor the next time he or she visits a particular Phone Power Web site. Cookies also allow us to tailor our Web sites to better match visitors' interests and preferences. Visitors may choose to disable Cookies by changing their browser settings; however, they may not be able to access some of the information on our Web sites. 

**Links:** Phone Power Web sites contain links to other Web sites. Phone Power is not responsible for the privacy practices of these Web sites. We encourage our visitors and customers to read the privacy policy of each Web site they visit. This Privacy Policy applies solely to information collected on Phone Power Web sites. 

**Sharing:** Phone Power may partner with other parties to provide specific services, such as billing solutions, which are designed to enhance the functionality of our products and services. When a customer signs up for these services, Phone Power will only share names or other contact information that is necessary for the third party to provide these services. 

**Special Cases:** It is Phone Power’s policy not to use or share the personal information about visitors or customers in ways unrelated to the ones described above without also providing you an opportunity to opt out or otherwise prohibit such unrelated uses. However, Phone Power may disclose personal information about visitors or customers, or information regarding your use of the Services or Web sites accessible through our Services, for any reason if, in our sole discretion, we believe that it is reasonable to do so, including: to satisfy laws, such as the Electronic Communications Privacy Act, regulations, or governmental or legal requests for such information; to disclose information that is necessary to identify, contact, or bring legal action against someone who may be violating our Acceptable Use Policy or other user policies; to operate the services properly; or to protect Phone Power and our customers. 

**Correction/Updating Personal Information:** If a customer needs to update or change personal identification information, Phone Power will help the customer to correct, update or remove personal data provided to Phone Power. The customer can update or change personally identifiable information using the Account Manager on our website <http://www.phonepower.com/account/> or by contacting our customer service department at (888)607-6937. 

**Responses to Email Inquiries:** When Visitors or Members send email inquiries to Phone Power, the return email address is used to answer the email inquiry we receive. Phone Power does not use the return email address for any other purpose and does not share the return email address with any third party. 

**Notification of Changes:** If we make any changes to the Phone Power Privacy Policy, we will post those changes on Phone Power Web sites so customers/visitors are informed. We will always use information in accordance with the Phone Power Privacy Policy. 

**Questions:** Any questions or comments regarding privacy should be sent to [[email protected]](https://web.archive.org/cdn-cgi/l/email-protection#5e2d2b2e2e312c2a1e2e3631303b2e31293b2c703d3133) or mailed to: 

**Customer Service**  
PhonePower  
9221 Corbin Ave. Suite 155  
Northridge, CA 91324
